<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ctf on Kenny Nguyen (momo)</title>
    <link>https://momo1239.github.io/tags/ctf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ctf on Kenny Nguyen (momo)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://momo1239.github.io/tags/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BYUCTF PWN Challenge Writeups</title>
      <link>https://momo1239.github.io/2024/pwnctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://momo1239.github.io/2024/pwnctf/</guid>
      <description>BYU CTF 2x PWN Challenge Writeup Link to youtube video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zlso9DMZXAc&amp;amp;t=596s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANS Offensive Operations CTF - Pwn Writeup</title>
      <link>https://momo1239.github.io/2024/sans_ctf_writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://momo1239.github.io/2024/sans_ctf_writeup/</guid>
      <description>SANS Offensive Operations CTF This was a challenge in the pwn category of the SANS Offensive Operations 2024 CTF. This is a writeup for the challenge &amp;ldquo;Warmup Pwn&amp;rdquo;. Unfortunately, I did not take any screenshots or save the challenge files so I&amp;rsquo;ll mainly be walking through what I did and the script I made.&#xA;Warmup Pwn - First Look The challenge tells us to connect using nc warmup.pwn.site 5005. They provide us with two files: target and libc-2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering Level 3 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://momo1239.github.io/2023/re3-writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://momo1239.github.io/2023/re3-writeup/</guid>
      <description>Reverse Engineering L3 Writeup This is part of a course called Fundamentals of Software Exploitation designed to teach students about exploitation development and vulnerability research. There are various modules and at the end of the modules are three progression challenges. This is the final progression challenge for the Reverse Engineering module.&#xA;Challenge Description Challenge / Response&#xD;Wow, stealing acquiring software is hard work... This one communicates with a server of some kind and makes you submit a ton of valid request-response pairs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
